<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivitiesChallange</string>
    <string name="text_1">Text-1</string>
    <string name="text_2">Text-2</string>
    <string name="text_3">Text-3</string>
    <string name="heading">Click any one button</string>
    <string name="first_paragraph">Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Learning Realm International (LRI) school is a Trust-run residential-cum-day english-medium co-ed institution, founded on Falgun 12, 2044 BS (February 24, 1988 AD) by the veteran educationist with reason and vision, Mr. Shiv Raj Pant. It imparts holistic education from Pre-Primary to Higher secondary levels with the following goals. Providing ‘world-class education’ to become a globalized citizen. Offering a stimulating environment for the inherent talent in students get explored for their holistic development. Developing competent human resource capable of meeting the challenges of identity at national and international level. Transforming each pupil into noble citizens imbibing universal human culture, values, and beliefs for healthy social life. Empowering every student rise beyond the average level of performance and ‘strive for excellence’. The school has ever been on robust move with a team of committed professionals pursuing these goals through quality education.</string>
    <string name="second_paragraph">Today, Trinity International College is the leading college in Nepal for +2 and A Levels. The College offers qualitative +2 programmes and Cambridge International A Levels at the higher secondary stage. It also runs programmes at the graduate and post-graduate levels - Tribhuvan University BSc CSIT, BBS, and BA as well as MA (English).

We provide the best available higher learning and all-round opportunities to all our students, invariably the best in the country, as they aspire to realize their personal talents and to expand their scholastic abilities. Our organization concentrates, first and foremost, upon academics supplemented with extracurricular and co-curricular activities. It also places great emphasis on personal development and individual counseling linked to course studies and career guidance and invites parental participation.

Trinity stands for academic accomplishment. It has an environment that fosters academic achievement. Student requirement and academic support go hand in hand. The College has a state-of-the-art infrastructure along with a reputed faculty. This educational establishment is managed by a devoted team of professionals advised by outstanding national and foreign advisors.

Above all, Trinity has most successfully developed a distinctive culture of excellence. The College does its best to fulfill the immediate and future needs of its commendable student community. This leading scholastic institution sees to it as its responsibility, and resolve, to equip its pupils with an education that is most relevant to their society and to their time.

For all this, Worthy placements here or abroad. These accomplishments of our alumni are indeed a testimonial to their worth and a matter of deep abiding pride to their alma matter.</string>
    <string name="third_paragraph">The British College strives to be a world-class college in Nepal offering British and international qualifications equipping our graduates with the knowledge, skills and values they need for success in the global job market and becoming creative entrepreneurs. In this regard we have a distinctive identity as the pioneering global college in Nepal. We offer reputed UK degrees and courses which are relevant to the current job market, enhancing each and every student’s employability.



We attract the best and the brightest students and, consequently, TBC offers an unforgettable academic experience transcending international boundaries with thought-provoking incision. Being the pioneering international college in Nepal, we also provide our students with unparalleled exposure and experiences both within and outside Nepal.



The defining characteristic of The British College is the local-to-global approach in the provision of our degrees and courses. Student exchange programmes and internships with multi-national companies serve as highlights of this unique student experience. Staffed by tutors and administrative personnel from the UK and Nepal, the College provides a premium education in Nepal.



The British College offers Undergraduate Programmes and Postgraduate Programmes which are awarded by UK universities: University of the West of England (UWE) and Leeds Beckett University (LBU).</string>
    <string name="top_heading">Click any button</string>
    <string name="text_one">Text one</string>
    <string name="text_two">Text two</string>
    <string name="text_three">text three</string>
    <string name="paragraph_content">Paragraph Content</string>
</resources>
